{
    "id": "201e2609d7f6493a9b976e46d8bc2393",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The event has been ………………………… until next week.",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone.",
            "answers": [
                "put out",
                "put off",
                "put down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1fee15c07c554299b6d800c45f175822"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ………………………….. your coat. I am taking you to the doctor.",
            "description": " To put on is to wear",
            "answers": [
                "put on",
                "put out",
                "put in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f9c145de9d5e4ac8b77d4de49559c3ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… the toys once you have finished playing with them.",
            "description": "To put away is to store for future use.",
            "answers": [
                "Put away",
                "Put off",
                "Put in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "baf74c2232dc46898c44871825fd9e71"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………….. the fire in the basement of the building.",
            "description": "To put out is to extinguish.",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "put out",
                "put down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f741bb40100948fdb871727403a8aa8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are planning to ……………………………. a fence around the property.",
            "description": "To put up is to erect.",
            "answers": [
                "put over",
                "put up",
                "put in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9490ee47e1dd4f0d9ac285c40296571b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. a lot of effort to succeed in her business.",
            "description": "To put in is to invest.",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "put in",
                "put out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c48949ef4e654b908e5d1e2967a5e3fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can no longer ……………………………….. his insolence.",
            "description": "To put up with something is to tolerate it.",
            "answers": [
                "put out with",
                "put up with",
                "put off with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87f7c20f76b34510857d26ed92c97e81"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………. the whole neighborhood but nobody had seen my cat.",
            "description": "To ask around is to ask the same question to a lot of people.",
            "answers": [
                "asked around",
                "asked out",
                "asked in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "627868d9249b4783a8f2afa3f8d9c3b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had a small …………………………… yesterday.",
            "description": "To get together is to meet.",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "get together"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5c2f93e6ff04e4ca53a153853e070a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The noise …………………………….. after some time.",
            "description": "When noise dies down, it becomes weaker.",
            "answers": [
                "died over",
                "died down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb21c0c8269f4108be61008cd0456fcb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The scheme ............................... for want of support.",
            "description": "When something falls through, it fails.",
            "answers": [
                "fell off",
                "fell out",
                "fell through"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "775a62b113614d6c9864e8334a39e023"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly the wheel .................................... the bicycle.",
            "description": "To come off is to become detached. ",
            "answers": [
                "came over",
                "came off",
                "came out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f46131a90bec4312b4df13a8111387f5"
        }
    ]
}